redmineup.com 2019-02-27

# Privacy Policy

**Last updated: 16th May 2018**

  * Privacy Policy
    *       * Information We Collect
      * How and why do We use collected Information?
    * Protection of Personal Data by RedmineUP
      * Performance of Your Rights
      * Data Security
      * Data Storage, Transfer and Technical Solutions
      * Information provided to our Users
      * Children
      * Data Collected by our Users
      * Third-Party Software
      * Third-Party Embedded Code
      * Contacting Us
  * Cookies Policy
    *       * How do We protect Your Information
      * How to manage cookies
      * Changes to Privacy Policy
      * Your acceptance of these Terms

Welcome to RedmineUP's Privacy Policy.

RedmineUP (“We”, “Our”, “RedmineUP”) is on your side in the fight for the privacy and control over you data in the Internet. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to both our Internet websites (“Websites”), including www.redmineup.com, www.demo.redminecrm.com, and our Cloud Hosting Services (the “Cloud”).

This Privacy Policy governs Our data collection, processing, and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding use, access, and correction of your personal information. Our goal is to provide transparency, understanding, and clarity on how personal data is processed at RedmineUP.

By using the Websites or the Cloud, you consent to the data practices described in following Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described here, you should not use the Websites or the Cloud.

We applied all means possible to comply with the recent regulations appointed by European Union — General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Below we gather all the information regarding the information we collect, ways and reasons why we do so, as well as Our cookies policy. Please refer to the [general Terms and Conditions](https://www.redmineup.com/pages/terms-and-conditions), to understand regulations related to use f this website, as well as [Licensing information](https://www.redmineup.com/pages/terms-and-conditions#licensing).

Our Privacy Policy does not cover any third party services. To learn about their practices, please visit their respective websites and get acquainted with their privacy policies documentation.

Shall you have any questions, please reach to us at support@redmineup.com.

### Information We Collect

We collect and process information only on your request, on the legal basis of your consent via following points of touch.

  1. Trial Registration form. 
  2. Helpdesk Widget form
  3. LiveChat widget
  4. Request to receive a newsletter 
  5. Request to access Demo version
  6. Request to download the „Redmine Theme” (free of charge)
  7. Request to download the „Light Version” (free of charge)
  8. Order placement. Upon placing an order, you will be redirected to order processing partner – 2Checkout, Inc. (formerly Avangate). Connections are run over secure SSL encrypted protocol and secured by Norton Antivirus and Firewall software. We do not collect nor process your data. To learn more about their approach to security of your information, please refer to 2Checkout’s privacy policy.

### How and why do We use collected Information?

We use information collected through our Websites as described in this Policy or on our Websites. For example, we may use your information to: 

  1. Improve our services or plugins, Websites and how our organization operates;
  2. Understand and enhance your experience using our Websites, and Services
  3. Provide services at your request;
  4. To process, manage, complete, and account transactions;
  5. Provide support and respond to your requests, comments, and inquiries;
  6. Invite you to participate in customer research or feedback;
  7. Create and manage online accounts you establish in the Cloud, Trial of the Cloud and Product Licenses;
  8. Send you related information, including transactional information, confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, support and administrative messages;
  9. Deliver you publications and newsletter, where we share knowledge and experience
  10. Communicate with you about promotions, upcoming events and news about products and services offered by RedmineUP and our selected partners; Please be advised that we might send information from such partners, but we do not share any of your data.
  11. Link or combine it with other information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service;
  12. Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards, policies, and our terms of use;
  13. Protect, investigate and deter against the fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity.

## Protection of Personal Data by RedmineUP

### Performance of Your Rights

Your data is stored and processed only with your consent. It will be stored in our database for the indefinite period (unless you agreed differently). GDPR grants expanded rights for individuals in the European Union to execute appointed rights.

At any given time you have the right to request: 

  1. access to your personal data;
  2. correction of your data;
  3. erasure of your data;
  4. restriction of processing;
  5. data portability.

To perform any of your rights, please send us a message at support@redmineup.com.

Your request will be resolved in a timely and effective manner, up to thirty (30) days. We might contact you to arrange details of your request.

Removal of your data will not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

You may opt out (unsubscribe) from receiving any emails from RedmineUP by following the Unsubscribe link in the footer of our emails. Even if you opt out, we may send you transactional or administrative messages, such as emails regarding about your account or our business relationship.

You may also send requests about your contact preferences, changes, request to opt-out from sharing your personal information with third parties by email sent to support@redmineup.com.

### Data Security

We value your data, as much as our own personal information. That’s why we adopted appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices as well as rigorous security measures, including data encryption.

### Data Storage, Transfer and Technical Solutions

We use third-party vendors and hosting partners for hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run our Websites and the Cloud.

Your personal data is stored in secured networks accessible by a very limited number of people with special administrative access these systems.

Hardware infrastructure that stores and processes your data is located in the territory of Republic of Ireland (European Union). All partners and territories where RedmineUP process data ensure an adequate level of protection of the mentioned data.

### Information provided to our Users

We may display the following information to users who sign-in (authorize) ou our Websites, according to their access level and point of touch: first name, user email, product name, purchase date and license number.

### Children

If you are under 18, or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you reside, you may only use the RedmineUP Website and Products with the consent of your parent or legal guardian.

### Data Collected by our Users

As you use our Services, you may import into our platform personal data that you have collected from your Clients or other individuals. We have no direct relationship with your Customers or any person other than you, and for that reason, you are responsible for making sure you have the appropriate permission to collect and process information from those individuals.

If you are a Subscriber and no longer want to be contacted by one of our Users, please opt out directly from that Member’s correspondence or contact the USer directly with the request to update or delete your data.

### Third-Party Software

RedmineUP uses third-party tools to provide us with services that support our business, such as Google’s tracking technology and LiveChat communication tool.

Those third parties might need access to specific information to operate. We rigorously monitor these vendors to limit the range of data they can access to a minimum that’s necessary for them to perform their contracted tasks.

### Third-Party Embedded Code

In our Websites, we use embedded third-party code: Youtube and Vimeo videos, and social media sharing buttons. That software operates according to the third party’s privacy policy and service conditions. We don’t control the range of data and the way third-party vendors are processing them. To learn more, please refer to the service provider’s website.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about any Policy please contact us at support@redmineup.com or send us a postal mail to our corporate address.

RedmineUP principal place of business is at Myasnitskaya ul. 13, str. 18, 101000 Moscow, Russian Federation.

Our Websites use various tracking methods, such as cookies, retargeting tags, web beacons and other technologies to receive information that may include personal data from your browser (such as IP-address, unique cookie identifier; device type; domain, browser type and language, operating system and system settings; country and time zone; previously visited web pages; information about your interaction with our Website; and access times and referring URLs).

We use cookies to track usage of the Websites and to understand visitors preferences and to be able to provide relevant advertising.

The advertising and analytical tools provided by our third-party partners do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, address or telephone number and cannot link usage data with your personal information.

Third parties may also collect information via our Website through their cookies, plug-ins, and widgets. These third parties collect data directly from your web browser, and the processing of this data is subject to their privacy policies.

Third-Parties cookies that can be enabled to use on our Websites: Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager, Google AdWords, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, LiveChat, Yandex.Metrica, 2Checkout (previously Avangate), Vimeo, YouTube.

Some of the cookies might be placed only if you use specific features or select particular preferences.

### How do We protect Your Information

We adopt strict data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in the Cloud or at our Websites. Our data protection procedures have positively pass external audit and examinations.

### How to manage cookies

Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies.

If you set your browser to reject cookies, some functionality of our Websites will be unavailable.

For more information about the cookies, please refer to the help pages for each browser. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We have the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When revised, we will updates date at the top of this page. We will inform you about the most significant changes. Still, we encourage you to periodically check this page for any changes to stay told about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy and be aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these Terms

By using our Websites, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Websites. Your continued use of the Websites indicates that you agree to the stated terms of use.

### Get Access to the Licence Manager

Please enter your e-mail address below. The access link to the Licence Manager will be sent to a given e-mail.
